Finding Aid for the Jesse Ely Wills Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Nicholas Hobbs Inventory
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0210
135 linear feet
- Council of Representatives (Box 1)
- Advisory Committee on State Legislation (Box 1)
- Board of Directors (Box 1)
- Materials from 40th Anniversary Meeting (Box 1)
- Anniversary Program (2 folders) (Box 1)
- Southern Society (bills paid) (Box 1)
- Division Seminar (Box 1)
- Faculty Manual (Box 1)
- Students (Box 1)
- Program Committee Reports (Box 1)
- "Integrated and Segregated Schools on Military Posts in the (Box 1)
- South: A Research Proposal" (Box 1)
- European Trip (Box 1)
- Counseling Service (Box 1)
- Department Seminar (Box 1)
- Principles of Personal Counseling (Box 1)
- Psychology 101 (course materials) (Box 1)
- General Psychology (course materials) (Box 1)
- Psychology 612: Group Counseling (Box 1)
- Education 449B: Carnegie Seminar (Box 1)
- Division Staff Meetings (Box 1)
- Reprints on Aging (Box 1)
- Education 555A: Human Development and Guidance (course materials (Box 1)
- and student papers) [folder one] (Box 1)
- Education 555A [folder two] (Box 1)
- American Psychology Association Meeting (Box 2)
- American Psychology Association Annual Meeting, 1955 (Box 2)
- American Psychology Association Annual Meeting, 1954 (Box 2)
- Board of Directors (Box 2)
- Fillmore Sanford (Box 2)
- Board of Directors (Box 2)
- Board of Directors (Box 2)
- Correspondence (alphabetically; incoming) (Box 2)
- Miscellany: American Psychology Association Meeting of Board of Directors, 1955 (Box 2)
- F American Psychology Association - Expenses (Box 3, Folder 6.0)
- D American Psychology Association - The Brayfield Problem (Box 3, Folder 6.0)
- American Psychology Association - Committees, Boards and Representatives to Other Organizations Reporting Through Board of Directors (Box 3, Folder 6.01)
- American Psychology Association - Secretaries of State (Box 3, Folder 6.02)
- American Psychology Association - Secretaries of State Association (Box 3, Folder 6.2)
- American Psychology Association - Corresponding Committee of 50 (file previously sent to Bob Holt) (Box 3, Folder 6.3)
- Convention Committee (Box 3, Folder 6.4)
- Convention Speaker (Box 3, Folder 6.04A)
- American Psychology Convention Program Committee (Box 3, Folder 6.04B)
- American Psychology Association - Committee on Child Psychology (Box 3, Folder 6.5)
- American Board of Examiners in Professional Psychology (Box 3, Folder 6.6)
- ABEPP - Policies and Procedures Booklet (Box 3, Folder 6.06A)
- Committee on Scientific and Professional Aims of Psychology (Box 3, Folder 6.7)
- History of Psychology Group (Box 3, Folder 6.8)
- Committee on Equality of Opportunity in Psychology (Box 3, Folder 6.9)
- Board of Professional Affairs (Box 3, Folder 6.20)
- Board of Scientific Affairs (Box 3, Folder 6.21)
- Education and Training Board (Box 3, Folder 6.22)
- Joint Commission on Correctional Manpower and Training (Box 3, Folder 6.23)
- Budget and Finance (Box 3, Folder 6.24)
- Clark Committee (Box 3, Folder 6.25)
- Cybernation Committee (Box 3, Folder 6.26)
- Ethics (Box 3, Folder 6.27)
- Ribicoff's Bill (Box 3, Folder 6.28)
- Washington Report (Box 3, Folder 6.29)
- Journals (Box 3, Folder 6.3)
- Publications Board (Box 3, Folder 6.3A)
- Journal of Education Psychology (Box 3, Folder 6.31)
- Journal of Counseling Psychology (Box 3, Folder 6.32)
- Contemporary Psychology (Ann Sanford) (Box 3, Folder 6.33)
- Journal of Abnormal Psychology (Box 3, Folder 6.34)
- Other Divisions (Box 3, Folder 6.4)
- Society of Psychological Study of Social Issues (Box 3, Folder 6.41)
- Division of Educational Psychology (Division 15) (Box 3, Folder 6.42)
- Division of Counseling Psychology (Division 17) (Box 3, Folder 6.43)
- Division of Clinical Psychology (Division 12), Preconference Materials (Booklet) (Box 3, Folder 6.44)
- Division 12 Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 6.44A)
- Division of Clinical Psychology (Box 3, Folder 6.44B)
- History of Psychology in Autobiography (Box 3, Folder 6.7)
- Bill 756 (Testimony of Hobbs and Supporting Materials) (Box 3, Folder 6.8)
- Social Influences on the Standards of Psychologists (Box 3, Folder 6.9)
- Booklets and Handbooks (1965; 1964) (Box 4, Folder APA)
- APA General Matters (Box 4, Folder 6.0)
- APA Board of Directors (Box 4, Folder 6.0A)
- APA Brochure
- APA Program
- APA Invitation List
- APA Arrangements
- APA Displays
- APA Building (Box 4, Folder 6.0C)
- APA Insurance Issue (Box 4, Folder 6.0E)
- Individual Student Life (Box 5, Folder 10.21)
- Doctoral Candidates, Music (Box 5, Folder 10.23)
- Doctoral Committees
- Prospective Director of Child Study Center
- Professional Students - National Science Foundation People (Honorable Mention) (Box 5, Folder 10.24)
- Screening Reports for M.A. People (Box 5)
- Committee on Psychological Resources in the South
- Acknowledgments of Report
- International Committee on Ethics
- Other Organizations
- American Association for the Advancement of Science
- Committee on Psychological Resources in the South
- Lilly Endowment
- Cooperative Program in Education Administration in Southern States
- National Science Foundation
- Southern Regional Education Board
- Tennessee State Public Health Association
- Ford Foundation
- American Association of University Professors
- Mental Health Guidance Center
- Southern Regional Council on Mental Health Training and Research
- Conference Board of Association Research Councils
- Convalescent Children
- Family and Children's Service (Box 5)
- National Institute of Mental Health Committee
- Committee on Education of Exceptional Children
- Teachers of Exceptional Children
- American Association for Gifted Children
- (Reprints) National Character (Box 5)
- Items - Social Science Research Council (Box 5)
- Counseling
- The Bulletin - World Federation for Mental Health (Box 5)
- Bulletin - NYSPA (Box 5)
- Carnegie Corporation of New York (Quarterly Report) (Box 5)
- Association for Higher Education/ So They Say About Higher Education (Box 5)
- ETS, Developments (Box 5)
- Higher Education and National Affairs
- Committee on the Judiciary United States Senate
- Bulletin - Educational Research Corporation (Box 5)
- Information Bulletin: Federal Security Agency - Survey of APA Members (Box 5)
- First Conference on Mental Health Services Pertaining to
- Tennessee Public Schools
- Theoretical Bases for Psychrometric Tests "Why Guidance?" (Box 5)
- Rational and Irrational Man
- Education: Child Guidance (Box 5)
- Conference on Non-Intellectual Determinants of Achievement (Box 5)
- School and Society - Child Development and Language Learning (Box 5)
- Handicapped Children and Youth Research Branch (Moss) (Box 6)
- Subcommittee on Construction of University-Affiliated Facilities for Mental Retardation (Hylton) (Box 6)
- Office of Education P.L. 85-926 (Kepple and Mackie) (Box 6)
- Application Forms for Grants from Children's Bureau (Box 6)
- Health, Education and Welfare Department Correspondence (Box 6)
- HEW Application for Public Health Service Grant
- HEW Department Directories (2 folders) (Box 6)
- Booklets for Department of NIH (2 folders) (Box 6)
- McGraw-Hill General Correspondence (1955-1959) (Box 6)
- McGraw-Hill General Correspondence (1960-1963) (Box 6)
- McGraw-Hill General Correspondence (1964) (Box 6)
- National Advisory Mental Health Council (roster) and Travel Expenses (Box 6)
- NAMH Correspondence (2 folders) (Box 6)
- NAMH Correspondence (Special Reports) (Box 6)
- A Theoretical Approach to Psychotherapy as Personality (Box 6A)
- Modification (Box 6A)
- The Multiple Discriminant Function: A Symposium (Box 6A)
- Catalogues and Book Announcements (Box 6A)
- Manuscript: Carl R. Rogers, "Some of the Directions and End (Box 6)
- Points of Therapy" (Box 6)
- Research
- Gifted Children: Project B Intensive Study (Box 6)
- Gifted Children: Project A Identification (Box 6)
- Seeman's Play Therapy Study (Box 6)
- Harvard University Project
- Harvard Report
- Harvard Project
- USPHS Creativity Project
- CBR Project
- USPHS Research Grants - General Announcements (Box 6)
- The Behavior of Small Groups
- Ford School Psychology Grant
- Book: General Psychology (Box 6)
- Multiple Contact, Persons Project (Box 6)
- Mental Deficiency Professors
- Educational Testing Service
- Special Education
- U.S. Office of Education (Box 6)
- Quincy Youth Development Commission
- Programs of Psychology - Other Universities (Box 6)
- National Research Council
- Education 220PA Examinations
- Southern Regional Educational Board
- Educational Research Corporation Bulletins
- Test Service Bulletins
- AIR Situational Tests of Leadership
- American Institute of Research
- AIR Research Notes
- Case of Mr. Weiss (Box 6)
- Group Therapy
- Individual Counseling
- Appraisal of Individual - Test Scores (Box 6)
- Appraisal of Individual - Psychology 595 (Box 6)
- General Correspondence (6 folders) (Box 6B)
- General Correspondence: Child Study Center (Box 6B)
- Reports on Child Study Center from Neville
- Mental Retardation - Research (Box 6B)
- General Correspondence (IMRID) (Box 6B)
- Research Efforts (IMRID) (Box 6B)
- Budgets
- General Correspondence (Psychology) (Box 6B)
- Faculty Minutes
- Self-Study Psychology Department (Box 6B)
- Colloquia Programs, Consultant, Schedules, etc. (Box 6B)
- Materials on Graduate Study in Psychology at Peabody
- Journal Holdings in the Psychology Reading Room
- Graduate Faculty in Psychology, (December, 1966) (Box 6B)
- Doctoral Candidates in Psychology
- Applications for Secretarial Positions
- 50th Anniversary
- Clinical Training Committee Minutes
- General Correspondence (Special Education) (Box 6B)
- Doctoral Graduates in Special Education
- Graduate Instruction Committee
- Scholarship Committee
- Committee on International Activity
- Ford Program Committee
- Nashville Center - Education Improvement Project (Southern (Box 6B)
- Association) (Box 6B)
- Committee on Graduate Education Study
- A & I Guidance Center (Box 6B)
- Grants and Fellowships (Guggenheim, Fulbright-Hayes, NASA) (Box 6B)
- Sabbatical and Research Quarters
- Summer Program on Creativity (1962) (Box 6B)
- Doctoral Dissertation - Hold File, Garland Millet (Box 6B)
- Carnegie Foundation Proposal
- U.S. Office of Education Proposal Research Center, IMRID (Dunn) (Box 6B)
- Pamphlets and Literature to Accompany D - Correspondence APA Miami Conference (November, 1958) (Box 7)
- APA Secretary's Meeting With National Voluntary Agencies APA Board of Professional Affairs (Box 7)
- APA Committee on Scientific (1960) (Box 7)
- APA Task Committee on Sub-Doctoral Education (Box 7)
- APA Task Committee on Psychology in Rehabilitation
- APA Board of Directors
- APA Education and Training Board
- APA Council of Representatives
- APA Division 12 Convention Program (1960) (Box 7)
- APA Division 12 Convention Program (1960), Proposed Symposia (Box 7)
- APA Symposia - Accepted (Box 7)
- APA Papers - Accepted (Box 7)
- APA Symposia - Rejected (Box 7)
- Abstracts of Proposed Research Papers
- APA Papers - Rejected (Box 7)
- APA Division 12 Convention Program (1961) (Box 7)
- APA Division 12 Presidential Address (1961), Sources of Gain in Psychotherapy (Box 7)
- APA Division 12 Committee on Nominations and Elections APA Division 12 and Division 17 - Joint Committee on Psychologists in Public Service APA Psychologists in Public Service (Box 7)
- APA Annual Meeting (1960), report of Ad Hoc Committee on Rules of Council (Box 7)
- APA United States Court of Appeals
- SREB - General Correspondence (August 1957 - December 1959) SREB - General Correspondence (January 1960 - ) (Box 7)
- SREB - Expense Account Forms (Box 7)
- SREB - Mental Health Training and Research Council (Correspondence) (Box 7)
- SREB Mental Health Training and Research Council (3 folders) (Box 8)
- SREB Mental Health Training and Research Council - Program and (Box 8)
- Review, (May, 1958) (Box 8)
- SREB Mental Health Training and Research Council (March, 1960) (Box 8)
- SREB Daytona Beach (August, 1958) (Box 8)
- SREB Williamsburg Conference j
- SREB Research Advisory Committee Meeting (Atlant~ January, 1961) (Box 8)
- SREB Committee on Research in Higher Education
- SREB Workshop on Mentally Ill and Emotionally Disturbed (Atlanta (Box 8)
- January, 1960) (Box 8)
- SREB Mental Health Forum
- SREB University of Georgia (March, 1958) (Box 8)
- SREB Regional Action
- SREB State Legislation Memos - Nashville Mental Health Center (Box 8)
- Association (2 folders) (Box 8)
- Site Visit - Master's Nursery Incorporated, New York City [MH 01379] (Box 8)
- Temporary File - Gra~ts (Box 8)
- Advisory Committee Regional Training Conference - Region (Box 8)
- V-Detroit, 1963 (Box 8)
- NIMH - General (Box 8)
- Correspondence (D - Z) (Box 9)
- Hogg Foundation (Box 9)
- Old Purchase Orders (Box 9)
- Case Histories (Box 9)
- Vanderbilt University Cooperative Study of Material and Infancy (Box 10A)
- Nutrition (Box 10A)
- Vanderbilt University Mental Retardation Center (Box 10A)
- -Ad -Ho-c Committee - Common Calendar Council on Academic Affairs (Box 10A)
- NCATE (Box 10A)
- Peabody Self Study (Box 10A)
- Peabody Self Study (1969-19.70) - Task Forces (Box 10A)
- Heart, Cancer, and Stroke Institute (Box 10A)
- Peabody Regional Laboratory (Box 10A)
- College Committees (miscellaneous) (Box 10A)
- College Committee Assignments (Box 10A)
- Policy and Planning Committee (Box 10A)
- Instruction Committee (2 folders) (Box 10A)
- Case Histories (Box 10B)
- Memorandums (A - Z) (Box 10B)
- Memorandum - Dean Robb (Box 10B)
- Memorandum - Dean Jones (Box 10B)
- Memorandum - Dr. Hill (Box 10B)
- Faculty Meetings
- Peabody College - General (Box 10B)
- General Planning
- Peabody College Committees
- Peabody Library
- Personality Theory 1
- Courses
- Child Study Center
- Workshops (Summer, 1954) (Box 10B)
- Guidance Conference (Summer, 1954) (Box 10B)
- Catalog Materials
- Division Planning - General (Box 10B)
- Ford Foundation
- General Education Program
- Admissions Processing Sheets (1956-1957) (Box 10B)
- M.A. Questionnaires (Box 10B)
- National Institute of Mental Health
- Tennessee Professorship
- Vocational Rehabilitation
- General Announcements and Bulletins
- Qualifying Examinations
- Comprehensive Examinations (nothing in folder) (Box 10B)
- Graduate Record
- Doctoral Aptitude
- Miller Analogies
- Mi~nesota Teacher Attitude Inventory (Box 10B)
- History - Stanley's Study of M.A. Recipients (Box 10B)
- Report of Departmental Action on D9ctoral Students
- Counseling Psychology Vanderbilt University Vouchers
- Sheets for Reporting Grades
- Ph.D. and Ed. Forms (Box 10B)
- Travel Requests
- Request to take Preliminary Examination
- USPSH - Mental Deficiency Project (Box 10B)
- Counseling Psychology (Box 11)
- USPSH - Project on Group Psychotherapy (1952) (Box 11)
- Miscellaneous (2 folders) (Box 11)
- Dade County Survey (Box 11)
- Division Problems (Old) (Box 11)
- Meeting of Florida Association of Deans and Counselors (Box 11)
- Methodist Counseling (Box 11)
- Counseling Services (Box 11)
- Hoge, John (Box 11)
- Internship Facilities (M.D. Project) (Box 11)
- Mental Deficiency Project Inactive File (Box 11)
- Conference on Teaching of Foreign Languages (1953) (Box 11)
- Recommendations (Box 11)
- Student Committees (Box 11)
- Jobs for Students (Box 11)
- Doctoral Screening Examination Scores (Box 11)
- Programs - General Planning (Box 11)
- Application Blanks (Box 11)
- Dem - Starkman (Box 11)
- Speal, Stanley A. (Box 11)
- Klaus, Rupert A. (Box 11)
- Def - Starkman (Box 11)
- Dec - Starkman (Box 11)
- Deg - Starkman (Box 11)
- Bill Lewis (Box 11)
- Bills (forms) (Box 11)
- Bills sent (Box 11)
- Contact sheets (Box 11)
- Counseling Center - General Announcements (Box 11)
- Invoices (Box 11)
- Memorandum on Rooms (Box 11)
- Post cards (Box 11)
- Release slips (Box 11)
- Summary sheets (Box 11)
- Det - Klaus (Box 11)
- ded - Starkman (Group) (Box 11)
- Deh - Starkman (Box 11)
- Dep - Starkman (Box 11)
- Bah - Heber (Box 11)
- Dat - Lewis (Box 11)
- Bim - Gardner (Box 11)
- Det - Balevre (Box 11)
- Bie - Acree (Box 11)
- Bij - Acree (Box 11)
- Bip - Starkman (Box 11)
- Gray -Bon (Box 11)
- Gray - Bir (Box 11)
- Seeman - Bam (Box 11)
- Seeman, Cab (Box 11)
- Seeman, Group - Bom (Box 11)
- Seeman, Daw (Box 11)
- Seeman, Cel (Box 11)
- Cic - Stokes and Seeman (Box 11)
- Cal - Stokes (Box 11)
- Cep - Stokes (Box 11)
- Cam- Duwall (Box 11)
- Col. D - Duwall (Box 11)
- Bem - Duwall (Box 11)
- Fab- Duwall (Box 11)
- Duwall and Paar, Zim (Box 11)
- Summary Sheets Completed (Box 11)
- Unassigned Cases (Box 11)
- Counseling Service (2 folders) (Box 11)
- Case Studies (50 folders) (Box 12)
- Inventory of Test Closet (Box 12)
- Fall Quarter Preliminary Materials (Box 12)
- Mrs. James Tabb (Box 12)
- Booklets on Peabody (Box 12)
- English 219PA - Examinations (Box 12)
- Clark, Eva Mary (Box 12)
- Room Assignments Sheets (Box 12)
- Conference on Higher Education (Box 12)
- Likert: A Program of Research on the Fundamental Problems of Organizing Behavior (Box 12)
- The Personal Counselor (Box 12)
- Pierre the Pelican Series (Box 12)
- Report of the Committee on Psychotherapy of the Division of Abnomal and Clinical Psychology (Box 12)
- Correspondence (A- Q) [18 folders] (Box 12)
- Correspondence (R - Z) (Box 13A)
- Correspondence - Intra-College (Box 13A)
- Correspondence - Official T.C. (Box 13A)
- Correspondence - Students (2 folders) (Box 13A)
- Doctoral Candidates (Others) (Box 13A)
- Doctoral Candidates (General) (Box 13A)
- Correspondence - The American Board of Examiners in Professional (Box 13A)
- Psychology, Incorporated (Box 13A)
- Correspondence - American Association for the Advancement of Science (Box 13A)
- The American Association for Gifted Children (Box 13A)
- American Jewish Committee (Box 13A)
- Correspondence - APA (Box 13A)
- American Veterans Committee (Box 13A)
- Correspondence - Aviation Psychology Program (Box 13A)
- Correspondence - The Citadel (Box 13A)
- APA - Committee on Therapy (Box 13A)
- Correspondence - Citizens and Southern National Bank (Spartanburg, South Carolina) (Box 13A)
- Correspondence - Commission on Mental Health Education (Box 13A)
- Doctor of Education Committee (Box 13A)
- lnterprofessional Council on Mental Health (Box 13A)
- Correspondence - Louisiana State Law Institute (Box 13A)
- National Committee for Mental Hygiene (WFMH) (Box 13A)
- Correspondence - New York Academy of Science (Box 13A)
- Correspondence - New York Life Insurance Company (Box 13A)
- New York Society of Clinical Psychologists (Box 13A)
- New York State Psychological Association (Box 13B)
- Occupations - The Vocational Guidance Journal (Box 13B)
- Correspondence - Ohio State University (Box 13B)
- Correspondence - Pennsylvania Mutual Life Insurance Company (Box 13B)
- Remsen Press (Box 13B)
- Richmond University Center (Box 13B)
- Correspondence - Society for the Psychological Study of Social (Box 13B)
- Issues (Box 13B)
- Correspondence - Southern Society for Philosophy and Psychology (Box 13B)
- T.C. Committee on Evaluation (Box 13B)
- Correspondence - Teachers Annuity (Box 13B)
- Correspondence - United Nations (Box 13B)
- Clinical and Abnormal Psychology, Division of (Box 13B)
- Correspondence - U.S. Army (Box 13B)
- University of North Carolina (Box 13B)
- Correspondence - Veterans Administration (Box 13B)
- Correspondence - Welfare Council of New York City (Box 13B)
- Group Therapy (Summer, 1950) (Box 13B)
- Course: Education 282M - Student Rosters (Box 13B)
- Course: Education 282M - Supplies and Equipment (Box 13B)
- Course: Education 381M - Techniques of Counseling (Box 13B)
- Counseling and the Individual (Box 13B)
- Psychology, Medicine and Legislature (Box 13B)
- Disturbed Children in France (Box 13B)
- Reflector (Box 13B)
- "of Mice and Children," a paper read to the Association for (Box 13B)
- Supervision and Curriculum Development, March 1, 1959; by Nicholas Hobbs (3 copies) (Box 13B)
- Miscellaneous envelopes of materials (3) (Box 13B)
- Ohio State University Guidance Conference (March 16, 1957, at 9:30 a.m.; "The Compleat Counselor" (Box 14)
- Special Education Seminars (Box 14)
- The Health Handi~apped Child (Box 14)
- Seminars (Box 14)
- Seminar in Educational Problems - Carnegie Group (Box 14)
- Psychology 445: Psychology of Personality (Box 14)
- The Speech and Hearing Handicapped Child (Box 14)
- The Blind Child (Box 14)
- The Gifted Child (Box 14)
- Gifted Children - General (Box 14)
- Gifted Child - Cleveland Major Work Classes (Box 14)
- Davis Scholarship (Box 14)
- "Study of the Doctorate" (Box 14)
- Records of Dr. Weiss, recorded by Nicholas Hobbs (Box 14)
- Group Therapy Material (Spring) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #1: Dr. Hobbs (March 31, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #2:. Dr. Hobbs (April 5, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #3: Dr. Hobbs (April 7, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #4: Dr. Hobbs (April 12, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #5: Dr. Hobbs (April 14, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #7: Dr. Hobbs (April 21, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #8: Dr. Hobbs (April 26, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #9: Dr. Hobbs (April 28, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #10: Dr. Hobbs (May 3, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #11: Dr. Hobbs (May 5, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #12: Dr. Hobbs (May 10, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #13: Dr. Hobbs (May 12, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #14: Dr. Hobbs (May 17, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #15: Dr. Hobbs (May 19, 1948) (Box 14)
- Session #2 (April 5, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #16: Dr. Hobbs (May 24, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #17: Dr. Hobbs (May 26, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #18: Dr. Hobbs (June 2, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #19: Dr. Hobbs (June 7, 1948) (Box 14)
- Group Therapy #20: Dr. Hobbs (June 9, 1948) (Box 14)
- American Psychological Association (Box 15)
- Vocation Rehabilitation Conference (Box 15)
- Miscellaneous Committees (Box 15)
- APA Special Committees (Box 15)
- Division of Clinical and Abnormal Psychology (Newsletter) (Box 15)
- Division of Counseling and Guidance (Box 15)
- Pennsylvania Counselor Training Study (Box 15)
- S.P.S.S.I. (Box 15)
- Division of Maturity and Old Age (Box 15)
- Division of Educational Psychology (Box 15)
- School Psychologists Conference (Box 15)
- Division of Education and Training (Box 15)
- Medical Psychology (Box 15)
- APA - OVR Institute - Planning Committee Journals (Box 15)
- Southern Society for Philosophy and Psychology (Box 15)
- Southern Psychological Association (Box 15)
- State Board of Examiners in Psychology (Box 15)
- American Board of Examiners in Psychology (Box 15)
- Committee on Ethical Standards (Box 15)
- Committee on Counselor Training (Box 15)
- Middle Tennessee Association for Gifted Children (Box 15)
- Crickshank, W. (Box 15)
- Prospective Staff: Hudson, George R. (Box 15)
- Active Department Students (Box 15)
- Division of Human Development and Guidance (Box 15)
- Ethics Tale (Box 15)
- Prospective Staff: Free, John E. (Box 15)
- Prospective Staff: Spielberger, Charles (Box 15)
- Prospective Staff: Schummers, John L. (Box 15)
- Prospective Staff: Patterson, Gerald (Box 15)
- Prospective Staff: Ehart, Mary Elizabeth (Box 15)
- Prospective Staff: Barbe, Walter (Box 15)
- Prospective Staff: Byrd, Eugene (Box 15)
- Prospective Staff: Stordahl, Kalmer E. (Box 15)
- Prospective Staff: Perkins, Keith J. (Box 15)
- "Crank Letters" (Box 15)
- Dr. H.H. Thomas (St. Albans, London) (Box 15)
- Batts, William 0., Jr.: Doctoral Dissertation Proposal (Box 15)
- Prospective Staff: Berg, Paul (Box 15)
- Prospective Staff: (Box 16)
- Prospective Staff: (Box 16)
- Students (Box 16)
- Prospective Staff (Box 16)
- Withall, John (Box 16)
- Jacques, Howard (Box 16)
- Prospective Faculty (1962) (Box 16)
- Prospective Faculty (1961) (Box 16)
- Prospective Staff: Guidance (Box 16)
- Prospective Staff: Experimental (Box 16)
- Faculty: Bailer, Irving (Box 16)
- Faculty: Baumeister, Alfred (Box 16)